MICHAEL JUSTUS

Student B. Sc. Bussines Informatics

Kiesstr. 74, 64287 Darmstadt | +49 151 27253339 | mi.justus@icloud.com

CAREER SUMMARY:

Solution-oriented problem solver with a year of professional experience in infrastructure and several years of personal engagement with hardware. Excellent skills and enthusiasm for communication and teamwork. I have a strong talent for self-teaching and independently expanding my knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

kimeta GmbH

Working Student Infrastructure | February 2023 - Present

- Assisting colleagues with soft- or hardware issues
- Taking on small projects, such as software procurement
- Automating repetitive tasks
- Handling numerous small programming tasks
- Communicating with external partners

Bert & Daiber PartG mbB

Working Student Audit | September 2021 - January 2023

- Final invoice verification
- Administrative support
- · Assistance with technical issues

EDUCATION:

2022 - Heute | Technische Universität Darmstadt

Bachelor of Science - Wirtschaftsinformatik

2021 - 2022 | Technische Universität Darmstadt

Bachelor of Engeneering - Wirtschaftsingenieurwesen m.t.F. Maschinenbau

SKILLS:

- Languages: German, English, Russian
- Infrastructure Scripting
- App Development
- Web Development